Morning.
Dzień dobry.
-Good morning.
- Dzień dobry.
Okay.
No dobrze.
Write your name on the board.
Napisz swoje imię na tablicy.
As some of you have already heard a week ago,
Tydzień temu dowiedzieliście się, że dołączy do nas nowa uczennica.
here she is,
Proszę,
the new transfer student.
oto ona.
My name is Yuka Kageyama.
Nazywam się Yuka Kageyama.
Since it's fall of our second year,
Zaczyna się drugi semestr drugiej klasy,
I'll only be with you for half of high school.
więc będę z wami tylko przez połowę szkoły średniej.
I look forward to studying with you
Cieszę się, że będziemy się razem uczyć
until graduation.
aż do ukończenia szkoły.
Make friends, everyone.
Zaprzyjaźnijcie się.
Let's see.
Zobaczmy...
Your seat will be
Usiądziesz
in the very back, next to the window.
z tyłu, przy oknie.
-Okay. -Good.
- Dobrze. - Świetnie.
All right.
No dobrze,
We're one week into the second semester.
to drugi tydzień nowego semestru.
I hope you're out of your summer vacation mode now.
Mam nadzieję, że weszliście już w szkolny rytm.
But I bet you're still sleepy.
Ale pewnie jeszcze śpicie.
Hello.
Cześć.
Kageyama, are you interested in changing the world?
Kageyama, chcesz zmienić świat?
What?
Co?
Do you want to join Perfect, Kageyama?
Chcesz dołączyć do Idealnej?
Perfect?
Idealna?
Join us
Dołącz do nas.
in purifying this dirty world together.
Razem oczyścimy ten brudny świat.
EPISODE 5
ODCINEK 5
Kage...
Kage...
That guy made Kage vanish just now, didn't he?
Kage właśnie przez niego znikła, prawda?
What are you after?
Czego chcesz?
Say something!
Powiedz coś!
You couldn't do it earlier.
Wcześniej się nie udało.
Don't do anything dangerous.
Nie narażaj się.
Shut up.
Zamknij się.
Is this coke?
To cola?
Excuse me.
Przepraszam.
What is this all about?
O co tu chodzi?
You want us to drink this?
Mamy to wypić?
But he put some powder in it.
Ale on tam coś wsypał.
I'm sure it's poison.
To na pewno trucizna.
-Damn him. -It's not poison.
- Walić go. - To nie trucizna.
-What? -We should recall something
- Co? - Mamy sobie
while looking at this.
coś przypomnieć.
That's what this is about, right?
O to chodzi, prawda?
Kageyama, the girl who was sitting there, why did you make her vanish?
Kageyama, dziewczyna, która tam siedziała... Czemu ją stąd zabrałeś?
Did you get rid of her because she resisted?
Bo się sprzeciwiła?
So, don't do anything stupid, everyone.
Nie róbcie nic głupiego.
Do what this guy says.
Słuchajcie go.
You want to know all the things that we did
Chcesz wiedzieć o wszystkim, co zrobiłyśmy
as part of Perfect, don't you?
w ramach Idealnej, prawda?
Originally, the things Perfect did were for the sake of justice.
Zamierzałyśmy zaprowadzić sprawiedliwość.
Please understand that.
Zrozum to.
At first, we never did anything dangerous.
Zaczęłyśmy od bezpiecznych rzeczy.
All we did were good things.
Nie robiłyśmy nic złego.
But then Miho started going wild.
Ale potem Miho poniosło.
Hey! Sack-head Jerk-off!
Hej! Workogłowy debilu!
Take that fucking bag off your head right now!
Ściągaj z głowy ten pierdolony worek!
Kyoko.
Kyoko.
I don't know what you have against us,
Nie wiem, co do nas masz,
but under that mask,
ale pewnie
I bet you're getting off on hearing girls scream.
jarasz się tym, że dziewczyny krzyczą.
You're just a goddamn pervert.
Jesteś zwykłym zboczeńcem.
Distract him.
Odwróć jego uwagę.
Stab him from behind.
Dźgnij go od tyłu.
-You want out of here, right? -How about you?
- Chcesz wyjść, prawda? - A ty?
Bring it on, pervert!
Chodź tu, zboczeńcu!
Don't!
Nie!
No, I can't.
Nie chcę.
I said don't do that!
Nie rób tego!
No! Stop! Please don't do that!
Nie! Proszę! Nie rób tego!
Please don't do that! Please!
Proszę! Nie rób tego!
-No! -I'll drink it!
- Nie! - Ja to wypiję!
I'll drink it, so leave her alone.
Wypiję to, zostaw ją.
Kyoko.
Kyoko.
That's bitter!
Ale gorzkie!
-Are you okay? -Does it sting or anything?
- Jak się czujesz? - Parzy?
My mouth feels all sandy.
Jakbym miała piasek w ustach.
Is this some kind of drug?
To jakiś narkotyk?
It wasn't poison?
To nie trucizna?
It might be sleeping medicine.
Możliwe, że to lek nasenny.
I've been taking it a lot recently.
Ostatnio często je biorę.
Sleeping medicine?
Lek nasenny?
Shiho, give me Kage's phone.
Shiho, daj mi telefon Kage.
-I knew it. It's this, Memi. -What is that?
- Wiedziałam. Memi, to o to chodzi. - Co to jest?
#BADGUYSSLEEPDEEP #DVPRICKBLEACHHEAD #PERFECT
#ZBOCZEŃCYMOCNOŚPIĄ #IDEALNA
God damn, they're late.
Spóźniają się.
Are they really coming at eight o'clock?
Naprawdę miały przyjść o 20?
Let's snatch those girls in the room next door.
Złapmy te laski z pokoju obok.
You're a genius at it, man.
Jesteś w tym świetny.
What about that girl you did the other day?
Co z tą dziewczyną z wczoraj?
Her?
Z nią?
She didn't cry when I smacked her. It was awesome!
Nie płakała, kiedy ją uderzyłem. Było świetnie!
To get rid of stress lately, I just...
Żeby pozbyć się stresu, po prostu...
Bam!
Bum!
Nice.
Nieźle.
I use her as my punching bag.
Jest jak worek treningowy.
What a jerk!
Ale z ciebie drań!
-You really like that kind of thing. -That's bitter! Damn, this coke is bitter.
- Lubisz takie rzeczy. - Ta cola jest jakaś gorzka.
-Really? -Try it.
- Serio? - Spróbuj.
Call the staff.
Zawołaj obsługę.
I bet you put something in at the drink bar.
Pewnie coś nam dosypałeś!
I bet it was you!
Pewnie to ty!
Douche
Dupek
Dirtbag
Ścierwo
Scum
Śmieć
#Perfect
#Idealna
What is he doing behind us?
Co on tam za nami robi?
Write?
Mam pisać?
Write what?
Ale co pisać?
-Mana, write "perfect." -What?
- Mana, napisz „idealna”. - Co?
He might be checking our writing.
Chyba chce sprawdzić nasze charaktery pisma.
Why me?
Dlaczego ja?
Perfect
Idealna
It's not me! I didn't do it!
To nie ja! Ja tego nie zrobiłam!
Then why did you remember that post?
Więc dlaczego to pamiętasz?
When we brought up sleep medicine and cola,
Kiedy zaczął się temat coli i leków nasennych,
I knew it had to be that post.
wiedziałam, że chodzi o to.
-But it wasn't me! -Then who was it?
- Ale to nie ja! - A kto?
It was Miho and Mao.
Miho i Mao.
You've been blaming them since they are gone.
Od kiedy znikły, ciągle je oskarżasz.
No, I'm not! It's true. Right, Memi?
Nie! To były one, prawda, Memi?
Don't get me involved!
Mnie w to nie mieszaj!
I'm not part of this!
Nie mam z tym nic wspólnego!
I'm sorry!
Przepraszam!
I invited them to the karaoke place.
Zaprosiłam ich do tego baru karaoke.
Miho told us to do that.
Miho nam kazała.
She said it's for Perfect and she wanted help.
Powiedziała, że chodzi o Idealną i potrzebuje pomocy.
So she gave me his number
Dała mi numer telefonu
and told me to invite them to karaoke.
i kazała ich zaprosić do baru.
I just followed orders.
Wykonywałam rozkazy.
I swear! Believe us!
Przysięgam! Uwierz nam!
Who the heck is the sack-head?
Kim jest ten workogłowy?
Don't ask me.
Skąd mam wiedzieć?
Most likely, it's one of those four guys.
To pewnie jeden z tych czterech.
What were their names?
Jak się nazywali?
-Their names? -I don't remember.
- Oni? - Nie pamiętam.
-Are you serious? -Wait. Remember?
- Naprawdę? - Zaraz. Pamiętacie?
I think she said they're Souou guys.
Oni chyba byli z Souou.
Souou? You mean Souou High School?
Z liceum Souou?
Yes. They're all delinquents there.
Tak, tam są sami przestępcy.
Do you remember how one of those guys had bleached hair?
Pamiętacie, jeden miał tlenione włosy.
Miho told me that a girl from our class
Miho powiedziała, że dziewczyna z naszej klasy
had been dating that guy.
umawiała się z nim.
She dated a guy from Souou High School?
Z facetem z liceum Souou?
Apparently, he hit and kicked her. He beat her up pretty bad.
Podobno ją pobił. Nieźle oberwała.
Miho heard a rumor about it.
Miho słyszała takie plotki.
She wanted to use Perfect to shame them.
Chciała, żeby Idealna się z nimi rozprawiła.
So, is Sack-head that blond guy?
Czyli workogłowy to ten blondyn?
Are you sure it's the blond guy?
Jesteś pewna, że to on?
Shiho?
Shiho?
Would he do this just because we wrote on his face?
Zrobiłby to wszystko tylko dlatego, że popisałyśmy mu twarz?
Well...
Cóż...
-He might. -What?
- Może. - Co?
After that video was posted on Perfect,
Kiedy ten filmik pojawił się na Idealnej,
that blond guy called me.
blondyn do mnie zadzwonił.
Seriously? I didn't know that.
Naprawdę? Nie wiedziałam.
He was really pissed off. He said, "I'll kill you for messing with me!"
Był wściekły. Groził, że mnie zabije.
-Kill you? -Why didn't you tell me that?
- Zabije? - Czemu nic nie powiedziałaś?
I'm sorry. But I told Miho.
Wybacz. Powiedziałam Miho.
What happened?
I co dalej?
She said, "They're all talk. Don't worry about it."
Powiedziała, że on tylko tak gada i mam się nie przejmować.
But there are always fights at that school.
Ale w tamtej szkole ciągle są bójki.
-I know. I thought about that too. -Then why didn't you tell me?
- Wiem, pomyślałam o tym. - To czemu mi nie powiedziałaś?
So, Sack-head might come back?
Czyli workogłowy może wrócić?
We have to get out fast!
Musimy uciekać!
Mirei.
Mirei.
What?
Co?
What do you think Sack-head wants to do with us?
Jak myślisz, czego on od nas chce?
I don't know.
Nie wiem.
Anyway, we have to think of a way out.
Ale musimy wymyślić, jak stąd uciec.
Check Kage's foot irons to see if there's anything unusual.
Sprawdź kajdany Kage. Może coś tam znajdziemy.
Kyoko, don't try anything dangerous again.
Kyoko, nie rób nic niebezpiecznego.
But you were trying to light this place on fire.
To ty próbowałaś wzniecić pożar.
I don't mind dying if it's with you, Kyoko.
Jeśli mam umrzeć z tobą, to w porządku.
But...
Ale...
don't you dare go and die,
nie waż się umrzeć
leaving me all alone.
i zostawić mnie samej.
Today was supposed to be our graduation day.
Miałyśmy dzisiaj kończyć szkołę.
I bet it will cause a huge uproar
Jestem pewna,
since all of us disappeared together.
że nasze zniknięcie zostało zauważone.
Even without this, our class is really fucked up.
Nawet i bez tego nasza klasa jest pojebana.
Miho disappeared before we did.
Miho zniknęła wcześniej.
And then there's our teacher.
No i ten nauczyciel.
You mean Hayashi?
Hayashi?
Mr. Hayashi was fired by the school.
Został zwolniony.
He won't be at the graduation ceremony.
Nie będzie go na zakończeniu.
That's right.
To prawda.
Was anything unusual?
Znalazłaś coś?
What is that?
Co to?
What is that sound?
Co to za dźwięk?
Are you from Souou High School?
Jesteś z liceum Souou?
Please! We had nothing to do with it!
Błagam! To nie my!
Get your revenge on Miho and Mao.
Zemścij się na Miho i Mao.
That's not it.
Nie o to chodzi.
Maybe
Może...
this has something to do with Hayashi.
chodzi o Hayashiego.
-Hayashi? -Mr. Hayashi?
- Hayashiego? - Pana Hayashiego?
You all know why Hayashi got fired, right?
Wiemy, czemu wyleciał, prawda?
I heard he beat up some kids.
Podobno pobił parę osób.
Could it be they were students from Souou High school?
Może to byli uczniowie z liceum Souou?
I heard that he used a bat.
Słyszałam, że użył kija.
A bat?
Kija?
You mean Hayashi beat up Souou students with a bat?
Hayashi pobił uczniów z Souou kijem?
In other news,
Kolejna wiadomość.
a high school teacher in his 40s in Yokosuka, Kanagawa,
Czterdziestoletni nauczyciel liceum z Yokosuki w Kanagawie
was arrested for beating up students from another school in the area.
został aresztowany za pobicie uczniów z innej miejscowej szkoły.
The teacher said that he did it to teach them a lesson.
Powiedział, że chciał dać im nauczkę.
The suspected culprit is
Podejrzany to
Tomoyuki Hayashi, a teacher at a private high school in the area.
Tomoyuki Hayashi, nauczyciel ze szkoły prywatnej.
According to the police report,
Według raportu policji
Mr. Hayashi said he got into an argument with them on the street
pan Hayashi zeznał, że wdał się w uliczną kłótnię z uczniami.
and pushed them without thinking they would be injured.
Doszło do przepychanek, lecz nie chciał nikogo krzywdzić.
However, the students said
Uczniowie zeznali jednak,
that the teacher beat them with an aluminum bat.
że nauczyciel pobił ich aluminiowym kijem baseballowym.
The police are continuing their investigation.
Dochodzenie trwa.
In other words, your foot
Czyli masz problem ze stopą,
was injured by Mr. Hayashi when he beat you with a bat?
bo pan Hayashi pobił cię kijem?
That's right, isn't it?
O to chodzi?
That's why you hate Hayashi, right?
Dlatego go nienawidzisz?
But that doesn't make sense.
Ale to nie ma sensu.
Why not?
Dlaczego?
If he held a grudge against Hayashi,
Jeśli masz problem z Hayashim,
why would he bring us all here?
co my tu robimy?
Well...
Może...
Maybe because we're Hayashi's students.
Może to dlatego, że nas uczył.
Just for that reason?
Tylko dlatego?
What other reason is there?
A jest inny powód?
And I still don't get the connection with the sleeping medicine incident.
Dalej nie widzę związku z lekami nasennymi.
Maybe he wants to know where Hayashi is.
Może chce wiedzieć, gdzie jest Hayashi.
Does anyone know?
Wiecie?
I don't know!
Ja nie!
-He left without even telling us. -You know his email address?
- Odszedł, nic nam nie mówiąc. - Znasz jego adres mailowy?
Mr. Hayashi's email address? No way.
Pana Hayashiego? Nie!
-What about this? -What?
- A co wy na to... - Co?
Maybe Hayashi was dating one of us.
Może Hayashi umawiał się z jedną z nas.
Are you kidding?
Żartujesz?
There's no way! He's so old.
W życiu! To staruch.
But Mr. Hayashi was a really dedicated teacher.
Ale był świetnym nauczycielem.
Some students idolized him.
Wiele uczennic go podziwiało.
So, instead of getting revenge on Mr. Hayashi,
Czyli zamiast zemścić się na nim,
you'll get revenge on his student?
wolisz się mścić na jego uczennicach?
There's no way that could be true!
Nie wierzę w to!
He's a loser who beat up kids, then quit!
To mięczak, który pobił uczniów, a potem odszedł!
Who would idolize that jerk?
Kto by go podziwiał?
Shiho.
Shiho.
Do you know anything about the beating that Mr. Hayashi was involved in?
Wiesz coś na temat tego pobicia?
I couldn't stand Hayashi.
Nie znosiłam Hayashiego.
He physically punished students.
Wymierzał kary cielesne uczniom.
I heard about it from the volleyball team.
Słyszałam o tym od siatkarek.
Most of them didn't like what he did.
Nie podobało im się to, co robił.
Me again?
Znowu ja?
I'll admit to the Perfect incident.
Przyznam się do działania Idealnej.
I'm the one who called and invited them to the karaoke place.
Ja do nich zadzwoniłam i zaprosiłam ich do baru karaoke.
But I don't know anything about what Hayashi did.
Ale nic nie wiem o sprawie Hayashiego.
I can't stand Hayashi either.
Też go nie znoszę.
I know some students idolized him,
Wiem, że niektóre uczennice go podziwiały,
but he really played favorites.
ale nie traktował uczniów sprawiedliwie.
He had a thing for you, Memi.
Ty mu się podobałaś, Memi.
What? Don't get me involved again!
Co? Czemu znowu mnie w to mieszasz?
I'll admit he gave me private lessons.
Przyznaję, że dawał mi prywatne lekcje.
I'm bad at physical education.
Jestem słaba z wuefu.
He's a dedicated teacher,
To dobry nauczyciel,
but he put his hands all over me.
ale zaczął mnie dotykać.
It really disgusted me.
To było obrzydliwe.
I really, really, really hated it.
Nie mogłam tego znieść.
See?
Widzisz?
We all really hate Hayashi's guts.
Wszystkie nienawidzimy Hayashiego.
We all think he's disgusting.
Brzydzimy się nim.
Hayashi...
Hayashi...
If you want revenge on Hayashi,
Jeśli chcesz się na nim zemścić,
there's no point in bringing us here.
przetrzymywanie nas tu nie ma sensu.
He was a total loser teacher.
Był beznadziejnym nauczycielem.
He was always saying, "Do your best."
Mówił, że mamy się starać.
Everyone laughed behind his back.
Wszyscy się śmiali za jego plecami.
What about you, Mirei?
A ty, Mirei?
Me?
Ja?
I didn't particularly hate Mr. Hayashi.
Pan Hayashi nic mi nie zrobił.
-Really? -But
- Nie? - Ale...
when I heard about his attack, I was disappointed.
kiedy usłyszałam o tej bójce, byłam zawiedziona.
He said he was teaching them a lesson,
Powiedział, że chciał dać im nauczkę,
but I think it's wrong to use violence for that kind of thing.
ale uważam, że przemoc to błąd.
So, naturally, I have no intention of defending him.
Więc oczywiście nie zamierzam go bronić.
He used that when Kage vanished.
Kiedy to wcześniej zrobił, znikła Kage.
Are you going to make Kumi vanish?
Teraz zniknie Kumi?
I've had enough!
Mam tego dość!
Memi?
Memi?
You must be kidding.
To jakiś żart?
Mr. Hayashi?
Pan Hayashi?
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
PRZEDSTAWIONY SERIAL JEST FIKCJĄ.
Subtitle translation by Brian Athey
Napisy: Arianna Sugier